In this section.
I'll just walk you through the code, which we are going to implement.
So I have prepared all the classes here.
You can download these classes from the download section.
So first is our Android service manager.
This is a simple class where we have a constructor and the print android function.
So the print android function just goes to print Android function, which is actually defined in the
Android service dot Java through the step.
Okay.
So this is our step i android service manager is to stub in this case.
And then we have the service class which actually defines the Android function.
In this case, we are just writing a log here and here I saw that we have a constructor which actually
instantiate context.
Okay.
And then we have a set of goals actually, which we need to copy and paste to register our service,
and then we have the ideal file.
It is actually a simple interface and this is actually used to create our steps.
This is our I Android service manager dot char which will campaign in job actually.
So we will generate this using Android studio in our next section.
Yeah.
So in the next section we'll just go ahead to.
So now it is in an empty class.
So in the next section we'll just go ahead and populate this.